<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IT | Academic</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tag/it/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tag/it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>IT</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>IT</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tag/it/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post about last week 5.0</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;last-weeks-post&#34;&gt;Last week&amp;rsquo;s post&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;monday&#34;&gt;Monday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had one remote couple, at which I gave a report. I hope he gets a high rating! And now I&amp;rsquo;m doing homework in all other subjects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tuesday&#34;&gt;Tuesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to go to the university (to write a test on matanalysis), then to the hospital and then to training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wednesday&#34;&gt;Wednesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday I was writing a test paper on analytical geometry. I hope I wrote it well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;thursday&#34;&gt;Thursday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the morning, I moved to the university to take the last laboratory on programming technology, as well as listen to two lectures on matanalysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;friday&#34;&gt;Friday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fridays are always hard for me, because we have four pairs in a row, and the last one ends at 19:20. I had to hand in an essay and my only debt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ps&#34;&gt;P.S.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading! Follow me so as not to miss the exits of new posts!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post about last week 4.0</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;last-weeks-post&#34;&gt;Last week&amp;rsquo;s post&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;monday&#34;&gt;Monday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had a day off on Monday. So I went for a walk with friends in the morning, then did my homework, and in the evening my friend and I went to the theater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tuesday&#34;&gt;Tuesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the morning I went to the university. The first pair we had was matanalysis, and the second was computer algebra. Then I went to training: there I ran a lot, did strength exercises, in general, spent time with benefits for my health. I enjoyed the day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wednesday&#34;&gt;Wednesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And on Wednesday we also had only 2 pairs in the morning - analytical geometry and mathematical logic. I adore these items, so time flies unnoticed for me on these pairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;thursday&#34;&gt;Thursday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the morning I came to the second pair - programming technology. It turned out to be interesting, we went through matrices and wrote some operators for them. Then we had a break, and after that - a couple of lectures on matanalysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;friday&#34;&gt;Friday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I decided to give myself the opportunity to relax, and I did not go to pairs on the translator module. I went to visit my uncle and did some homework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ps&#34;&gt;P.S.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading! Subscribe so as not to miss the releases of new posts!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post about last week 3.0</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;last-weeks-post&#34;&gt;Last week&amp;rsquo;s post&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;monday&#34;&gt;Monday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The week began with studying at a remote location. I earned points for being active at the lecture and went for a walk with friends. Then in the evening I had to fly back to Moscow. I returned late, but I flew without incident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tuesday&#34;&gt;Tuesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was interesting at the matanalysis today. Then I went to practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wednesday&#34;&gt;Wednesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I earned points for my activity at the mat seminar.logic, and also successfully passed the colloquium on analytical geometry for 10/10!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;thursday&#34;&gt;Thursday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I did everything I had planned and went to school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;friday&#34;&gt;Friday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to English classes, passed the papers. I cooked dinner and watched an interesting movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ps&#34;&gt;P.S.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading! Such posts will be published once every 3 weeks. Follow me so as not to miss anything interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post about last week 2.0</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;last-weeks-post&#34;&gt;Last week&amp;rsquo;s post&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;monday&#34;&gt;Monday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The week began with studying at a remote location. I listened to the lecture, then went to visit friends, did my homework. It turned out productively!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tuesday&#34;&gt;Tuesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The couples were interesting today. At the matanalysis, candy was distributed for the correct answers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wednesday&#34;&gt;Wednesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today are my favorite subjects! The day is beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;thursday&#34;&gt;Thursday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today we tried to fix an incorrectly working function in C++, and we did it. Hurray! In the evening we went to the cinema for a disaster movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;friday&#34;&gt;Friday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to English classes, passed the papers. And in the evening we went for a walk around the city center and went to have dinner in a cafe. The perfect end to the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ps&#34;&gt;P.S.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading! Such posts will be published once every 3 weeks. Follow me so as not to miss anything interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post about last week 1.0</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82-%D0%BF%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B4%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B8-%D0%BD%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;last-weeks-post&#34;&gt;Last week&amp;rsquo;s post&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;monday&#34;&gt;Monday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My week began with a school Monday at a remote location. I had two pairs in a row: mathematical logic and programming technology. Then I sat down for homework, of which, unfortunately, we have quite a lot. After finishing my homework, I went to the supermarket for groceries, and then I cooked food: my favorite cutlets with potatoes and a vegetable salad. In the evening, I was preparing for the next school day and went to bed relatively early, at 23:00, so that the next morning I could go to the first couple at my favorite university.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tuesday&#34;&gt;Tuesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the morning I woke up and realized that I had overslept and, of course, I did not go to university. I stayed at home, doing my homework again to free up the weekend for myself. And then I remembered that I was officially on sick leave and this day would not be considered truancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wednesday&#34;&gt;Wednesday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;March 8th! My friend and I went for a walk around the city, we were presented with a wonderful bouquet of tulips, we ate rolls and in the evening I went to the theater to see the play “Onegin”. The performance was truly gorgeous! I returned home late, immediately deciding that I would not go to the first couple on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;thursday&#34;&gt;Thursday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A miracle happened, and I went to the first couple! This day turned out to be great: the boys congratulated us on the last holiday, presented cupcakes and postcards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;friday&#34;&gt;Friday&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the morning I did my homework, and in the afternoon I went to the university for a speech on the Translator Module. We danced, and instead of couples we were allowed to go home. In the evening I was preparing a history report. Beautiful day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ps&#34;&gt;P.S.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading! Such posts will be published once every 3 weeks. Follow me so as not to miss anything interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
